<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CNC on Dimex</title>
    <link>https://dimex-mfg.com/tags/cnc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CNC on Dimex</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dimex-mfg.com/tags/cnc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CNC</title>
      <link>https://dimex-mfg.com/products/cnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dimex-mfg.com/products/cnc/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the forefront of precision engineering at Dimex. Our CNC machining services represent the pinnacle of advanced manufacturing, offering unparalleled accuracy, efficiency, and versatility for a wide range of industries.
CNC Machining: A Symphony of Precision: CNC (Computer Numerical Control) machining is the art of transforming raw materials into intricate components with the precision of computer-guided tools. At Dimex, our CNC machining services go beyond the conventional, providing a symphony of precision that meets the most demanding specifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDM (Electrical Discharge Machining) by Thread and Penetration</title>
      <link>https://dimex-mfg.com/products/edm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dimex-mfg.com/products/edm/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the cutting edge of precision machining at Dimex. Our EDM services redefine the possibilities with a specialized focus on thread machining and penetration capabilities. Unleash the power of Electrical Discharge Machining with us for intricate, high-precision components.
Thread Machining Mastery: At Dimex, we elevate thread machining to an art form. Our EDM thread machining services go beyond the ordinary, enabling us to craft threads with unparalleled precision and intricacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High-Production CNC Lathe</title>
      <link>https://dimex-mfg.com/products/lathe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dimex-mfg.com/products/lathe/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to a new era of precision manufacturing at Dimex. Our high-production CNC lathe services redefine efficiency and accuracy, delivering a superior solution for your high-volume machining needs.
Rapid Turnaround with High Efficiency: Experience the unmatched efficiency of our high-production CNC lathe services. Designed for high-volume projects, our CNC lathes ensure rapid turnaround times without compromising on precision. The automation features of our equipment streamline the production process, allowing for continuous operation and increased productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
