<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dimex</title>
    <link>https://dimex-mfg.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dimex</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dimex-mfg.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://dimex-mfg.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dimex-mfg.com/about/</guid>
      <description>MISSION: Offer the best solution in machining and metal-mechanical devices for the entire industry in general accompanied by the high quality of our products.
VISION: To be a leading company worldwide recognized for the high quality and precision that is handled in our products and services, satisfying the needs of our clients, positioning us as one of the Mexican companies in the metalworking industry developed by teamwork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNC</title>
      <link>https://dimex-mfg.com/products/cnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dimex-mfg.com/products/cnc/</guid>
      <description>Immerse yourself in the pinnacle of precision with our CNC machining services.
Our state-of-the-art CNC machines are equipped to handle a variety of processes, including milling, turning, and grinding.
What sets us apart is our unwavering dedication to achieving the tightest tolerances and maintaining optimal efficiency in every project.
At DIMEX, we transform your designs into reality with unmatched precision and attention to detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDM (Electrical Discharge Machining)</title>
      <link>https://dimex-mfg.com/products/edm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dimex-mfg.com/products/edm/</guid>
      <description>Embark on a journey of intricate design and unparalleled precision with our EDM services. Electrical Discharge Machining allows us to create complex shapes with micron-level accuracy.
This technology is particularly well-suited for projects that demand intricate detailing, and our skilled team ensures that every component meets the most stringent quality standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://dimex-mfg.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dimex-mfg.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>To contact us, please fill out the form below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
